Guide to the Music Department records, 1898-2004 RG0075
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Music Department records
1898-2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Dept. of Music
RG0075
19.5 Linear Feet
Collection includes programs, photographs, scrapbooks, correspondence, posters, meeting minutes, by-laws.
Box UP0006
Box UP0005
Box UP0004
Box UP0003
Box UP0002
Box UP0001
Box UP0007
Restrictions on Access
The unprocessed boxes UP0001-UP0006 have personnel records that are closed for 75 years from date of creation. Series 12, Box 1, folders 48-54 are closed for 50 years from date of record creation. They contain personnel files, as well as information about faculty hiring. Series 13 contains restricted student files, and are closed for 100 years from date of creation. Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Please see staff for assistance.
Box UP0007 contains uncataloged theses, dissertations and independent research projects.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Music Department.
Historical or Biographical Note
A formal Department of Music did not come into existence until 1964, although The George Washington University's musical tradition is deep. The Bachelor of Arts degree in music provides a broad base for understanding the role of music, both as a individual art form and in its social context, and ensures that students have basic skills in music. This degree lays strong foundation for the further pursuit of any aspect of music in graduate school. The B.A. program is one in which the future scholar, composer, theorist, and knowledgeable music lover is nurtured and trained. The Department also offers a Minor in Music, minor in Jazz Studies.
The department has a number of ensemble groups, the oldest of which are the Glee Club and Troubadours, which began in the early 1900's. Dr. Robert Howe "Doc" Harmon began directing the Men's Glee Club in the 1920's, then took the baton of the Women's Glee Club, and eventually created the combined men's and women's choruses over his forty year career. Throughout those years, his choral groups appeared at many major Washington events, including White House parties, Cherry Blossom Festivals, summer concerts on the Potomac, and Christmas tree-lightings.
Outside of Washington, they appeared at the "Singer Bowl" of the 1964 New York World's Fair, and many conventions and festivals throughout the eastern United States. Upon his retirement in 1964, the Department of Music was created, with George Steiner being its first chair. For more information on the history of the department, see the book titled "Through The Years: The History Of The GWU Choral Program" written in 1998.
Alumni formed the Harmon Choral Associates in 1986, under the direction of David Bates, class of 1946, and faculty member Cathy Pickar, which raised money to support the program. It continued until 2001.
The earliest record of choral activity at the University is found in the 1898 yearbook, The Columbiad. The Women's Glee Club, singing in the old University Hall, performed "Selection from the Geisha" and "Kentucky Babe." During those early years there were undoubtedly many impromptu vocal gatherings but the earliest record of a Men's Glee Club appears in 1899, when C.W. Whitemore was its director. By 1914, the Women's Glee Club was presenting chapel exercises and singing at Pan Hellenic parties. The Men's Glee Club, under the tutelage of Professor Swett, presented concerts and organized a mandolin section.
Dr. Robert Howe "Doc" Harmon soon was directing the Men's Glee Club, then took the baton of the Women's Glee Club, and eventually created the combined men's and women's choruses over his forty year career. Throughout those years, his choral groups appeared at many major Washington events, including White House parties, Cherry Blossom Festivals, summer concerts on the Potomac, and Christmas tree-lightings. Outside of Washington, they appeared at the "Singer Bowl" of the 1964 New York World's Fair, and many conventions and festivals throughout the eastern United States.
Troubadours, these days, are a select group of vocalists chosen from the ranks of the University Singers, but originally they were musical comedy performers. The troupe, organized in 1927, required members to have a prominent part in the cast for one year, or serve two years in minor roles, as staff members or as orchestra or chorus members. Many of the musical comedies were presented around town. This first Troubadours organization ceased activities in the 1930s. In the summer of 1950, Dr. Harmon and Professor Vincent J. DeAngelis formed the Traveling Troubadours, at the request of the chief of Personnel Services of the Military Air Transport Service, for the purpose of entertaining U.S. military personnel on our remote overseas bases. Members were selected from the ranks of the Glee Club on the basis of vocal ability, and the group varied in size from twenty to thirty voices. The Traveling Troubadours gave hundreds of shows in places like Thule (Greenland), Tokyo, North Africa and the Azores. They entertained a handful of GIs in a small-unheated airplane hangar at Frobisher Bay on Baffin Island, and they sang for a capacity audience in the Great Opera House in Reykjavik, the capital of Iceland. In 1960, they headlined for six weeks at New York's Radio City Music Hall.
Dr. Harmon retired as director in 1964. That same year the University Music Department began under the leadership of George Steiner. After Dr. Harmon's retirement Jules Zabawa was appointed director. He served until 1969 when Dale W. Krider replaced him. In 1970 Stephen J. Prussing became director and served until 1978.
In 1978, Professor Catherine J. Pickar became director of the Glee Club, which changed its name to the University Singers in 1981. The current Troubadours were reorganized under Director Catherine J. Pickar in 1981, with help from Melissa Maxman, her student assistant. This time, the group was based on the tradition of informal a cappella singing which originated at the British universities and continues at most northeastern U.S. universities, as well as some southern and west coast institutions. The members themselves arrange the group numbers between twelve and fifteen voices and most of its repertoire. Like the Traveling Troubadours of the 1950s the current Troubadours have served as ambassadors for the George Washington University by appearing at numerous events in the city of Washington and traveled under the auspices of the United States Information Service to Portugal in 1984 and Ireland in 1985. The next year the Troubadours toured France. In the spring of 1988, they made a trip to the west coast for the University, presenting concerts for alumni, parents and prospective students. Subsequent trips included Bermuda, California, Italy and New England in 1993. On March 22, 1986, Glee Club, University Singers and Troubadours alumni from places as distant as California, Iowa, Oklahoma, Florida and Texas gathered at The George Washington University to honor the memory of Dr. Robert Howe Harmon, director of GW's vocal ensembles from 1924 to 1964. The occasion was such a success that choral alumni organized the Harmon Choral Associates, launched the Harmon Fund and the Harmon Choral Prize Fund. A second Harmon Choral Reunion was held in 1990 and the third in 1994.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include programs, news clippings, photographs, itineraries, scrapbooks, correspondence, posters, meeting minutes, by-laws, articles, newsletters, and an LP album. They range in date from 1989-2004, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Chair of the Department of Music. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into six series: Musical organizations and performances, American songs, Choral programs, Office of Choral Activities, and two series titled Departmental files.
Washington (D.C.); Performances; Songs; By-laws; Scrapbooks; Events; Photographs; Choral music; Music; George Washington University
- Musical organizations and performances, 1926-2004; RG0075 Series 1; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains programs, flyers, brochures, newsletters, programs, correspondence, press releases, news clippings, postcards, and music scores. They range in date from 1926 to 2004. They concern the Glee club; choral activities; student, faculty, and visiting performances; the Troubadours; the GW Band; and the constitution for the Traveling Troubadours.
  - GWU Band, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Music Department, 02/22/1926 -11/20/2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Music Department - Choral Activities, 03/29/1981 -04/29/1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Music Department - Glee Clubs (To 1961), 1930-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Music Department Programs, 1961-1971, 11/14/1961 -12/08/1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Music Department Programs, 1972-1978, 02/11/1972 -12/04/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Music Department Programs, 1979-1994, 02/09/1979 -04/23/1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Music Department - Programs--Orchestra, 05/05/1965 -04/09/1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Music Department Report--Self study for National Association of Schools of Music, 1985, 03/11/1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Music Department Report--Self study for National Association of Schools of Music, 1990, 02/26/1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Music Department Troubadours (To 1961), 1928 -09/01/1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Music Department Troubadours (1961-1991), 03/28/1982 -04/11/1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- American songs, 1950; RG0075 Series 2; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains one LP album titled American Songs - songs sung by Margaret Truman (B.A. 1946) dated 1950.
  - Record LP Album - "American Songs", 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Sung by Margaret Truman (B.A. 1946)
- Choral Program, 1998; RG0075 Series 3; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains one compact disc, computer disk and booklet. The CD and booklet are titled "Through the Years: the History of the GWU Choral Program," and is dated 1998.
  - Program - Through the Years, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Floppy Disc copy of Program - Through the Years, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Compact Disc copy of Program - Through the Years, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - Troubadours, 1991-1994; RG0075 Series 10; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 2)
    This box contains photographs of the GW Troubadours' performance of "Cabaret" in 1996, trips to Italy in 1992 and 1994, U.S. Singers retreat and camp at Chesapeake Bay, and miscellaneous choral photographs.
- Office of Choral Activities, 1898-2001; RG0075 Series 4; 9.5 Linear feet (Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 13, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6)
  This series contains photographs, newspaper clippings, scrapbooks, correspondence, posters, tour itineraries, videotapes, newsletters, membership lists, reunions, meeting minutes, by-laws, and plaques. This material dates from the 1920s-2001.
  This material relates to the activities of the choral groups at GW. Subjects include: Harmon Choral Associates (Dr. Robert Howe Harmon, director of Glee Clubs); the photographs are of choral activities/toubadours, including trips to Italy, Prague, Iceland, Greenland, Bermuda the Cabaret 1996; miscellaneous notes and program from the Mikado (GW Women's Glee Club with the U.S. Air Force Band); and Choral Society performing Handel's Messiah in 1959. There are also photographs with Bob Hope and a note from Barbara Bush.
  Many items in the collections are photocopies of the originals.
  - The Columbiad, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Columbiad-Glee Club, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Columbiad - Glee Clubs, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Mall - Glee Clubs, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Mall - Glee Clubs, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Mall & The Cherry Tree, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Missing
  - The Mall, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Cherry Tree, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The GW News & The Cherry Tree - Girls Glee Club, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Hatchet - Glee Club, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - GWU Periscope - Glee Clubs, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Cherry Tree - Girls Glee Club, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Cherry Tree - Girls Glee Club, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GWU - Glee Club, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Cherry Tree - Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - GWU Program - Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Cherry Tree - Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Cherry Tree - Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The Cherry Tree - Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ONewspaper Clippings, Photo Program & Cherry Tree - The Men's Glee Club, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Program, Cherry Tree - Glee Club, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    formerly folder 25a
  - Program Letter from Mrs. Hoover, Letter, Newspaper Clippings - Troubadours & Men's Glee Club, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    formerly folder 25b
  - Photos, Newspaper Clippings Program- Men's Glee Club, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    formerly folder 25c
  - Program, Photos, Newspaper Clippings- Men's Glee Club, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    formerly folder 26
  - Probably The Cherry Tree - Troubadours and Glee Club, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    formerly folder 27
  - The Cherry Tree - Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    formerly folder 28
  - Probably The Cherry Tree - Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    formerly folder 29
  - The Cherry Tree - Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    formerly folder 30
  - Probably The Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    formerly folder 31
  - Probably Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    formerly folder 32
  - Probably Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    formerly folder 33
  - Probably Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    formerly folder 34; photographs mounted on a backboard
  - Probably Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    formerly folder 35
  - Probably Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs - Program, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    formerly folder 36
  - Probably Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    formerly folder 37
  - Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    formerly folder 38
  - Cherry Tree, Group Photo - Men's Glee Club, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    formerly folder 39
  - Cherry Tree, Program & - Glee ClubsPhotos of Men's and Women's Glee Clubs, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    formerly folder 40
  - The Cherry Tree - Women's Glee Club, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    formerly folder 41
  - Roster, The Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    formerly folder 42
  - The Cherry Tree - Glee Clubs, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    formerly folder 43
  - Card List of Glee Club Officers, Postcards, letters and envelopes, carbon copy of Treasurer's Report, Memo from Max Farrington, letter from Burton Davis of National Press Club, 'Alumni Review', Article on Dr. Harmon - GleeClubs and Glee Club Jamboree 1949 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    formerly folder 44
  - Dr. Harmon and Troubs (misc.) 1950s Newspaper Clippings, The Mikado, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    formerly folder 45
  - Brochures, Photo, copies of Traveling Troubadours' Constitution and Regulations; "Foreword" (Tribute to Dr. Harmon) - Traveling Troubadours, 1950-1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 46
  - Photos, Brochures, Newspapers and Newspaper Clippings (All of these re trips to Northeast Air Command) - Traveling Troubadours, 1950-1957 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 47
  - Newspaper Articles, Photos, Instructions (All re Trips to Iceland and Greenland) - Traveling Troubadours, 1950-1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 48
  - Brochures, programs, napkins, photos, newspapers, articles, maps (All re various trips - NEAC, Hawaii, Bedford Springs, Pa.) - Traveling Troubadours, 1950-1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 49
  - Many of the items are Bank statements, with uncounted items in envelopes - Traveling Troubadours, 1947-1958 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 50
  - OBanners, napkins, "Tips", Photos (Trips to Labrador and Thule), Maps - Traveling Troubadours, 1950-1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 51
  - Photos, Sheet Music re various trips - Traveling Troubadours, 1950-1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 52
  - Letters, Evening Star, Hatchet, Map, Cherry Tree (Trip to Labrador, Greenland, Newfoundland) - Traveling Troubadours, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 53
  - Letters, Newspaper, Hatchet, passport (Trip to Labrador, Greenland, Newfoundland)- Traveling Troubadours, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    formerly folder 54
  - David Lum's Photo Album of Pacific Tour - Many Photos - Traveling Troubadours, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 55
  - Photo album (probably David Lum's) of Tripsto North Africa and NEAC - Traveling Troubadours (empty), 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    formerly folder 56
  - Certificate, Hatchet, Alumni Review, Cherry Tree (Trips to Iceland or Greenland, Northwest USA and Alaska) - Traveling Troubadours, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    formerly folder 57
  - Newspaper, Certificates, Stamps, Fact Book, tips, Cherry Tree (re Trips to Iceland, Greenland, Newfoundland) - Traveling Troubadours, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 58
  - Banner, Newspaper article (Trips to Bermuda, Azores, Libya, NEAC) - Traveling Troubadours, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 59
  - Mostly Photos (Trips to North Africa) - Traveling Troubadours, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 60
  - List, Photo (Trip to Northeast Air Command) - Traveling Troubadours, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 61
  - Lists, Programs, Travel Orders, Newspaper accounts, Cherry Tree (Trips to NEAC, Thule)- Traveling Troubadours, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 62
  - Photos, Menus, Billeting Lists (Trips to NEAC) - Traveling Troubadours (empty), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 63
  - Mostly Photos, articles, travelogue (Trips to NEAC, Azores and Bermuda) - Traveling Troubadours, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 64
  - Letters, Newspaper, Hatchet, Alumni Review (Trip to Thule and Azores) - Traveling Troubadours, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 65
  - Hatchet, Schedule, Program, (All re trip to Bedford Springs, Pa.Iceland, Azores) - Traveling Troubadours, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    formerly folder 66
  - Forms, Photos, Newspaper, Cherry Tree (re trips to Thule, NEAC) - Traveling Troubadours, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 67
  - Lists, Hatchet, Programs, Photos, Cherry Tree(re various trips and concerts)- Traveling Troubadours, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    formerly folder 68
  - Cherry Tree, Newspaper, Letters and Photos (Re trips to Newfoundland and Maine) - Traveling Troubadours, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    formerly folder 69
  - Program, The Cherry TreeTraveling Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    formerly folder 70
  - Cherry Tree, Photos, Rehearsal Schedule, (Re general and local)- Traveling Troubadours and Glee Clubs, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    formerly folder 71
  - Cherry Tree, Newspapers, Hatchet, Letter - mostly Glee Clubs and mostly re Testimonial about Dr. Harmon, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 72
  - Newspaper Clippings, Photographs(missing), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 73
  - Newspaper Clippings, Photos, Testimonials, and Radio City Music Hall Programs - Traveling Troubadours, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 74
  - Newspaper Clippings, Photos (re trip to Radio City Music Hall) - Traveling Troubadours, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 75
  - Cherry Tree Photo - Glee Club and Troubadours, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 76
  - Cherry Tree, Photo - Glee Club and Troubadours, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 77
  - Traveling Troubadours, Madrigals (JuleZabawa), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 77a
  - Cherry Tree, Photo - Glee Club, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 78
  - Hatchet, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hatchet, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 78b
  - The Cherry Tree - University Chorus, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    formerly folder 79
  - The Cherry Tree - University Chorus, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    formerly folder 80
  - Newspaper Clippings - Obituaries of Dr. Harmon, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    formerly folder 81
  - 'New' Troubadours, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    formerly folder 82
  - Newspaper Clippings, Letter, Hatchet- 'New' Troubadours, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    formerly folder 83
  - Correspondence 'New' Troubadours, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    formerly folder 84
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence re 'New' Troubadours, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    formerly folder 85
  - Correspondence, Programs, Group of posters - 'New' Troubadours, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    formerly folder 86
  - Programs, Photos, GW Report, re trip to Portugal for most part - 'New' Troubadours, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    formerly folder 87
  - Notices re trip to Ireland - 'New' Troubadours, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    formerly folder 88
  - Brochures, Program, Photos re trip to Ireland - 'New' Troubadours, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    formerly folder 89
  - Correspondence, Newspapers re Trip to Ireland - 'New' Troubadours, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 90
  - Correspondence, Forms, Business Cards, re trip to Ireland - 'New' Troubadours (hereafter will drop word 'New'), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 91
  - Correspondence Program re trip to Ireland - Troubadours, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 92
  - Troubadours with Bob Hope, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Photo Album w/negatives; formerly folder 92a
  - OBrochures, Schedules re trip to Ireland - Troubadours, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 93
  - Brochures, schedules re trip to Ireland, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 93a
  - Choral Alumni Reunion, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 94
  - Book by Bishop Nolan Harmon (Dr. Harmon's brother - Autobiography, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 95
  - Lists, Photos, Correspondence - 1986 Choral Alumni Reunion (Box 6, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 96
  - Reunion - Photos, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 96a
  - Correspondence, Programs, GW Report - 1986 Choral Alumni Reunion (Box 6, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 97
  - Correspondence re trip to Soviet Union - Troubadours, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 98
  - Letters, Program, Photos - Troubadours, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 99
  - Cherry Tree, Correspondence, Sheet Music re trip to Bermuda - Troubadours, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 100
  - Brochures, Forms, Correspondence re trip to Bermuda - Troubadours, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 101
  - Forms, Letters, Brochures re trip to Bermuda -Troubadours, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    formerly folder 102
  - Cherry Tree, Itinerary, Letter re trip to California - Troubadours, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 103
  - Brochures, Maps, Programs re trip to California - Troubadours, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 104